gotapparel.com 2014-11-22

# GotApparel Privacy Policy| Shop GotApparel.com

### Privacy Notice

By visiting the GotApparel.com website or any other websites operated by GotApparel.com or its affiliates (collectively, the "Site"), you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Notice. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Notice, please do not use the Site.

Throughout GotApparel.com’s years of operation, we have developed relationships with our customers based on respect and integrity. We're aware of the trust and confidence you demonstrate when you visit the Site and provide us with information. This Privacy Notice is posted to demonstrate our leadership in online security and customer service practices. We treat your information with the same honesty and sensitivity that we have displayed throughout our company's history.

### 1\. Personal Information Collected By GotApparel.com

Gotapparel.com does not sell, share, or rent any of your information under any circumstances. Financial information such as your credit card numbers are never stored on our servers and are destroyed as soon as your order is placed. You can also use Paypal to shop with GotApparel.com. We use information that we collect from our visitors and customers to personalize and improve your visit and shopping experience at the Site. We gather the following types of information:

Information You Give to Us:

We Collect Personal Information that is provided by Site users. "Personal Information" includes your name, address, telephone number, credit or debit card information, e-mail address, IP address. Personal Information is collected when you establish an account with us, place an order on the Site, participate in a contest, sweepstakes or on-line survey, or when you communicate with any of our departments such as customer service, sales or technical services through the Site, telephone, mail or fax. In some instances, we may obtain other people’s names and email addresses that you may choose to provide as part of our "email a friend" feature.

Cookies:

Through the use of cookies, we may also collect and analyze the IP address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as your browser type and version; operating system and platform; purchase history; confirmation when you open e-mail that we send you; and the URLs which lead you to and around the Site including the date and time. You can generally set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie. Software is also available from third parties which will allow you to visit the Site without providing this information. You are welcome to use the Site if you use such software but we will not be able to offer you our personalized services and we will be unable to accept any online orders from you.

Orders:

If you place an order through the Site, you will be required to provide contact, billing, and payment information.

Catalog Requests and Email Newsletter Subscriptions:

Upon placing an order through the Site, you will automatically begin receiving both the GotApparel.com catalog and the GotApparel.com email newsletter, based on the Personal Information you have provided, unless you opt-out of receiving such communications. If you request an email newsletter subscription, we will send you an email confirming your request. This confirmation process allows you to unsubscribe if you change your mind and decide not to join the list. Furthermore, the confirmation email will alert you if someone else has entered your email address into our email newsletter subscription list. In order to make our email newsletters more relevant and useful to you, our servers may receive a confirmation when you open an email message from GotApparel.com.

### 2\. Use of Information Collected By Use

We use this information in an effort to improve your experience on the Site, to provide services to you and to communicate with you about information that you request. We may also use this information to help us target specific offers to you, to help us develop and improve our Site, and to tailor our Site to your interests.

### 3\. Sharing of Information with Third Parties

We will not rent, sell or otherwise disclose your Personal Information to unrelated third parties without your consent, except as stated in this Privacy Notice.

Service Providers:

We may employ other companies or individuals to provide certain services to or on behalf of us such as analyzing customer lists and data, or performing marketing or consulting services. These third parties ("Service Providers") will only have access to the information needed to perform these limited functions on our behalf and are required to provide your Personal Information with at least the same level of protection and security as we use on the Site. Such Service Providers are prohibited from using your Personal Information for any purpose other than that for which such party was engaged by us and/or as stated in this Privacy Notice. Any Service Providers that use data received from us may only do so in accordance with this Privacy Notice.

Credit Card Companies:

If you place an order through the Site, the Personal Information you provide is transmitted to your credit card company to verify and authorize your purchase. At certain times we may offer financing options with or without third party participation. If you use a financing option, information provided by you (such as your address, birth date, social security number, and credit card number) may be used to request a credit report from third parties or may be sent to a third party for processing.

Third Party Marketing Partners:

From time to time we might establish a business relationship with other third parties whom we believe are trustworthy. In such cases we might license, exchange, share and/or cross-reference information, including your name and postal mailing address that will enable such third parties to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you. We will never share any telephone number(s), e-mail addresses, or credit card information which you have given us with any such third party partner(s).

Related Companies:

We may share your postal and e-mail address; telephone number(s), customer preferences, and purchase history with other subsidiaries of our parent company, Global Sportswear. We will never share any credit card information which you have given to us with any of these related companies.

Aggregate Information:

We provide aggregate information to some of our business partners. This information is used in a collective manner and does not identify you individually in any way. We collect and share aggregate information in order to know more about the general profile of our customers so that we can improve your shopping experience.

Shippers:

If you make a purchase through the Site, your name, telephone number and shipping information must be provided to third party shippers such as UPS, FEDEX and the United States Postal Service to deliver your purchase. There also may be instances in which we drop-ship orders directly to you from one of our manufacturers or suppliers. These drop-shippers are only given your name, postal address, and telephone number for the sole purpose of fulfilling your order.

Third Party Transaction-Level Data:

If you visit the Site from a third-party website the third-party website may be able to access select information from your individual transaction information. In order to track and credit your transaction the third-party website may give you a unique code, cookie or graphic which will uniquely identify you. This will only happen if you link directly from a third party website to the Site. Any transactions made at the Site while such a code is active will be reported back to the third party website. We will only report non-Personal Information to these websites such as the date of the transaction, the product(s) purchased and the amount spent. We will not report any information to these third party websites that will allow them to personally identify you. The presence of a third party navigation bar at the top of any page on the Site is an indication that the third party website may be able to see your activity on the Site.

Links to Third Party Site:

The Site contains certain links to third party websites, such as our vendors. We are not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content found on these websites. We recommend that you check the privacy notice of each website you visit. Links to third party websites are provided solely for your convenience and any submission of data to such websites shall be at your sole risk.

Catalog Requests:

When you request a catalog from us, we share your name and postal address with a third party fulfillment company for the sole purpose of sending you the requested catalog. This third party is not permitted to store the information is only authorized to use this information to transmit catalogs to you.

Law Enforcement and Protection of Users:

To the extent permitted by law, we will disclose Personal Information to government authorities or third parties pursuant to a legal request, subpoena or other legal process. We may also use or disclose your information as permitted by law to perform charge verifications, report or collect debts owed, fight fraud or protect our rights or property as well as those of our affiliates, customers, or its users. You should be aware that, following disclosure to any third party, your Personal Information may be accessible by others to the extent permitted or required by applicable law.

### 4\. Affiliate Programs

We maintain relationships with third party affiliate websites. Although we do not and cannot control the activities of the third parties that operate such websites, we will cease doing business with any affiliate that engages in abusive practices, including, for example, spam, trademark infringement, predatory means of attracting visitors, or unlawful activities. To report abuse by an affiliate, please contact our Affiliate Manager via email at [affiliates@GotApparel.com](mailto:affiliates@GotApparel.com)

### 5\. Children and Privacy

The Site is a general audience website and is not directed to children under the age of 13. We will never knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide us with personally identifiable information of any kind whatsoever. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 13 and has submitted Personal Information without verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable information from our files. We understand that children may not fully understand all of the provisions of this Privacy Notice or make informed decisions about the choices that are made available to adult users of the Site. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be familiar with the websites they visit. GotApparel.com does not sell products to persons under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you are required to seek the consent of your parent or guardian to purchase products from the Site.

### 6\. Security

Joining Hands With GeoTrust enabled Gotapparel.com to provide you SSL Secured Website. Sites secured by QuickSSL are utilizing 128-bit SSL certificates thereby offering the highest level of encryption or security possible. This means you can rest assured that communications between your browser and this site's web servers are private and secure.

You should recognize, however, that no computer system is fully secure and that there are inherent risks associated with Internet transactions. To make sure you have the latest security features on your browser, you may want to download the most recent version of your favorite browser, which should have full SSL support.

### 7\. Corrections/Information Removal/Opt-Out

If your name, e-mail or postal address, telephone number or other Personal Information changes, you may update, correct or omit the relevant information by contacting us at [privacy@gotapparel.com](mailto:privacy@gotapparel.com). In addition, if you no longer wish to receive communications from us you may opt-out by emailing us at [privacy@gotapparel.com](mailto:privacy@gotapparel.com), sending a letter to: GotApparel.com Privacy Officer, 14938 Shoemaker Ave, Santa Fe Springs, CA 90670 or by clicking on the unsubscribe link within any marketing e-mail you receive from us. If you no longer wish to receive our catalog, you may call us at 1-866-847-8678, email us at [privacy@gotapparel.com](mailto:privacy@gotapparel.com) or send a letter to: GotApparel.com Privacy Officer, 14938 Shoemaker Ave, Santa Fe Springs, CA 90670.

### 8\. Contact Information

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Notice, please e-mail us at [privacy@gotapparel.com](mailto:privacy@gotapparel.com) or send a letter to: GotApparel.com Privacy Officer, 14938 Shoemaker Ave, Santa Fe Springs, CA 90670

### 9\. Business Transfer

GotApparel.com is a wholly owned subsidiary of Global Sportswear. However, in the event that GotApparel.com is sold, has its assets acquired or transferred, whether voluntarily or involuntarily, or merges or becomes affiliated with any other division, individual or entity, any customer information owned or under the control of GotApparel.com may be one of the transferred assets. We reserve the right, as part of such transaction, to transfer or assign the Personal Information and aggregate information we have collected from users of the Site.

### 10\. Limitations On Liability

In no event will gotapparel.com or its parent, affiliates, licensees or any party involved in creating, producing or delivering the site or its products or services be liable in any manner whatsoever for any incidental, consequential, indirect, special or punitive damages arising out of your access, use or inability to use the site, or in connection with any failure or performance, error, omission, interruption, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus or line or system failure (including loss of profits, loss of business or data, business interruption, and damages that result from inaccuracy of the information or inconvenience, delay, or loss of the use of the site). The foregoing limitations apply whether the alleged liability is based on contract, tort, negligence, strict liability or any other basis, even if gotapparel.com or its affiliates or any other party has been advised of the possibility of such damages.

### 11\. Google Analytics for Display Advertising

Gotapparel.com is committed to respecting the privacy of its customers and as mentioned earlier. We do not and will not share your personal information with any other website under any circumstances. We have enabled Google Analytics (Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting and DoubleClick Campaign Manager Integration) on this site to help Google display our ads and content based on your buying preferences, ads you want to see and actions you want to take on the internet.

To prevent your cookies from being collected and stop receiving interest-based ads from us on other websites, opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising by clicking [here](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).
